

CANDIDATE REPORT

Position: Wordpress Developer

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Name: Nguyen Gia Dan	DOB:
Gender: Male	Add: HCMC

OVERALL ASSESSMENT

Mr. Dan has over 9 years of experience as a PHP Web Application Developer, specializing in WordPress themes, plugins, and payment APIs. He has extensive experience in technical support and customizing WordPress sites. His work includes building systems using Docker and AWS for the Japanese market. Dan has a strong background in various web technologies including PHP, MySQL, and JavaScript. He has also developed notable themes such as FreelanceEngine and MicrojobEngine. Mr. Dan is proficient in troubleshooting and providing effective online communication. He holds a Bachelor's degree from HCMUS.

Regarding language proficiency, Mr. Dani used to work in an international work environment with a wide variety of clients therefore his English is good enough to work directly with foreigners.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

VNUHCM - University Of Science (HCMUS) (2006 - 2011)

- Major: Bachelor's degree

SKILLS

Technical skills:

PHP WordPress MySQL JavaScript

HTML/CSS Bootstrap Sass VueJS

Docker Git/Github cPanel/FTP Hosting Firebase

XAMPP/MAMPP Nginx/Apache



Soft skills:

- Technical support
- Customization services
- Excellent troubleshooting
- Internal training
- Online communication
- Time management

WORK EXPERIENCE

JVIT Apr 2023 - Jun 2024

PHP Developer

- Customize WordPress Project
- Laravel and Symfony for Japanese market
- Build on the local system using Docker or AWS

Freelancer Jun 2022 - May 2023

Fullstack Developer

- Customize WordPress site
- Implement payment gateway

EngineThemes Jun 2013 - Aug 2022

Senior WordPress Developer

EngineThemes is a WordPress application theme creator

- Converting HTML Templates into Fully functional WordPress themes.
- Implement payment gateway for WordPress themes and plugins.
- Technical support work directly with customers via email to help them solve problems.
- Offer Customization services for client
- Fix bugs and maintenance themes/plugins.
- Conduct internal training for developers within the team.

Tools and technologies: WordPress, XML, HTML/CSS, PHP & MYSQL, jQuery, Ajax,

Sublime/VS,Photoshop, Bootstraps, Sass.

Key achievement: FreelanceEngine theme, MicrojobEngine theme.

(+81) 45 228 9010 | Sales: (+81) 45 620 3807



Goscom Jun 2012 - May 2013

PHP/WordPress Developer

- Experience with Xampp (Linux, Nginx/Apache, MySQL, PHP, HTML/CSS).
- Convert PSD file to HTML/CSS template.
- Customize PHP WordPress/Woocommerce and support customers.

MAIN PROJECTS

FreelanceEngine (5/2015-8/2017)

Project Description	It is a WordPress freelancer marketplace theme, such as a clone upwork site.
Team Size	15
Position	WordPress Developer
Responsibilities	 Join the team to discuss function, UI/UX. Complete task(function) was assigned. Maintenance and build new function base on feedback Support customers via email.
Technologies used	PHP, WordPress, Bootstrap, Ajax, HTML/Javascript/jQuery, Sublime, cPanel, Xampp, Mysql, Apache/Nginx, Adobe Photoshop.

MicrojobEngine(6/2016-8/2019)

Project Description	It is a WordPress freelancer marketplace theme, such as a clone fiverr site.
Team Size	15
Position	WordPress Developer
Responsibilities	 Join the team to discuss function, UI/UX. Complete task(function) was assigned. Maintenance and build new function base on feedback Support customers via email.
Technologies used	PHP, WordPress, Bootstrap, Ajax, HTML/Javascript/jQuery, Sublime, cPanel, Xampp, Mysql, Apache/Nginx, Adobe Photoshop.



agentsync.com.au(5/2022-10/2023)

Project Description	Support customers build a website based on FreelanceEngine theme. Adding new functions, fix bugs or tester
Team Size	20
Position	WordPress Developer (part time).
Responsibilities	 Complete task(function) was assigned. Test and reproduce the problem then fixes bugs. Support team member via chat(english).
Technologies used	PHP, WordPress, Bootstrap, Ajax, HTML/Javascript/jQuery, Sublime, cPanel, Xampp, Mysql.